{
    "subject": "resource/Sunday_Calm",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Sunday Calm is a 1923 short silent comedy film directed by Robert F. McGowan. It was the 20th Our Gang short subject released.",
    "human_readable": "Sunday Calm is a 1923 short silent comedy film directed by Robert F. McGowan, which was also the 20th Our Gang short subject released.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8470678925514221,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Sunday Calm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8013035655021667,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Sunday Calm' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.762015163898468,
            "question": "What type of film was 'Sunday Calm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7545008063316345,
            "question": "How many Our Gang short subjects were released before 'Sunday Calm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.700455904006958,
            "question": "What was special about the release order of 'Sunday Calm' within the Our Gang series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6920114755630493,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Sunday Calm'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6564301252365112,
            "question": "Was 'Sunday Calm' a sound film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6450917720794678,
            "question": "What is the name of the film series that 'Sunday Calm' belongs to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5314780473709106,
            "question": "In what decade was 'Sunday Calm' made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3476872444152832,
            "question": "What does it mean for a film to be a short subject?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sunday Calm is a 1923 short silent comedy film directed by Robert F. McGowan, which was also the 20th Our Gang short subject released.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6364_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what decade was 'Sunday Calm' made?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6364_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film series that 'Sunday Calm' belongs to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6364_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was 'Sunday Calm' a sound film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6364_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6364_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that \"Sunday Calm\" is a 1923 short silent comedy film directed by Robert F. McGowan and it was the 20th Our Gang short subject released, thus supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}